thank you brother
thanks huh now we have to take a subway
old
on the way to the shark office
because we can fish in São Paulo
has to São Paulo with a box mount plan
wants to be on Uber
first we have to see if we
can enter
it's with Felipe
you are company
it's none i'm caio oh man this bro is the time
caraca brother and then there's bonzão Brother if there's Fábio Caio
if it goes well then bro we
manage to put a Charlie Brown here
man we were trying to switch
idea with Felipe is connected only he is in a meeting
and I don't even know if he'll make it
welcome us we are in this
Things there from
get this orientation
speaks brother to you Charlie Brown Junior
understood the first edible skateboard wheel
this one is for you too
I would speak hand you would speak
there's how I leave 1 Charlie Brown Ali
on that little table Ali to leave on titanium
is on
Charlie Brown Junior now
Philip of Alphaville directly
in the titanium of Felipe Tito malandragem
caraca here comes a lot of famous people
all the time is on and on the shelf
there's Charlie Brown from the time we go in this bro